Guide to the R. G. Davis Papers Relating to Dario Fo
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
R. G. Davis papers relating to Dario Fo
1950-2017
GEN MSS 1520
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
9.92
(10 boxes)
Fo, Dario
Davis, R. G.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Andover Street Archives on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2017.
Dario Fo
Dario Fo (1926-2016) was an Italian dramatist, theater producer and director, actor, singer, composer, artist, and political activist. He received the 1997 Nobel Prize in Literature.
Content Description
The R. G. Davis papers relating to Dario Fo, which span from 1950-2017, contain correspondence, writings, printed material, photographs, audiocassettes, audiovisual materials, and other papers by or relating to Dario Fo.
Dramatists; Theatrical producers and directors; Actors; Composers -- Italy
- Production material, 1979 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Contains newspaper clippings, a journal, handwritten and typescript notes, and photocopies.
- "Anarchist - New - Abbie Hoffman", 1979-1981 (Box 1)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, newspaper clippings, photocopies, a show program from Wyndhams Theatre (1981 May), and a show program from Half Moon Theatre (1979 April 12-May 5).
- Design and music - Anarchist, 1980 (Box 1)
  Contains Wolfgang Roth designs and storyboards, as well as typescript and handwritten notes.
- Income - Canada, circa 1980s (Box 1)
  Contains box office performance statements.
- Anarchist - Canada - Open Circle theatre, circa 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes and set directions.
- Anarchist - Cowan, Theatre Magazine translation, circa 1982 (Box 1)
  Contains photocopies of a translation of Accidental Death of an Anarchist, by Suzanne Cowan.
- Accidental Death script - Open Circle, Toronto, Canada, 1980-03-13 (Box 1)
  Contains script, adapted by R. G. Davis, based on the translation by Suzanne Cowan.
- Canada - assessed, 1980-03 (Box 1)
  Contains a typed assessement of the Canadian production within Toronto.
- Program - PR - Press Review, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  Contains newspaper clippings, programs, and flyers.
- Accidental Death - Richard British, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  Contains a letter and postcard, handwritten and typescript notes, 5th Festival of Italian Theatre in New York catalog, and Saturday Night, periodical (1980 January / Febraury).
- London - Belt and Braces Roadshow, script, 1979 (Box 1)
  Contains a journal, and an Accidental Death of an Anarchist script.
- Canada pics - Open Circle theatre, 1980 (Box 1)
  Contains contact prints, negatives, instant film photographs, handwritten notes and typescript notes.
- Belt and Braces, correspondence and handwritten notes, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- NYU - Brosius / Combination, corrected script, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Accidental Death - Act. I - Italian, original and [Suzanne] Cowan, corrected English-language script, 1980 (Box 1)
- Anarchist - Act. II, circa 1980s (Box 1)
  Contains handwritten notes, a corrected script, and newspaper clippings.
- Accidental Death - Canada / Toronto, reviews, newspaper clippings and photocopies, 1980-03 (Box 1)
- Accidental Death of an Anarchist - Tony Mitchell script, 1980 (Box 1)
- TCG (Theatre Communications Group) - Fo, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings and a copy of the Theatre Communications periodical, vol. 5, no. 2 (1983 February).
- Anarchist - Los Angeles reviews, photocopies of newspaper clippings, 1983-01 (Box 1)
- Celestino de Iuliis version, 1979 (Box 1)
  Contains material regarding Celestino de Iuliis' translation. Includes handwritten notes, correspondence and a corrected script.
- Joe Taubmann / Fo - legal letters, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Accidental Death of an Anarchist, bound script, 1980 (Box 1)
- San Francisco Mime Troupe (Joan Holden) version, 1981 (Box 1)
  Contains a corrected "We Can't Pay, We Won't Pay" script, newspaper clippings and correspondence.
- BTB - article / We Won't Pay, 1981-09 (Box 1)
  Contains a typescript copy of Bonnie Borenstein article, "Dario Fo's We Won't Pay, We Won't Pay and the American Working Class."
- We Can't Pay, We Won't Pay, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  Contains a script for "We Can't Pay, We Won't Pay," handwritten notes, correspondence, and magazine and newspaper clippings.
- Photos - Fo, N.Y., 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains photographic and contact prints from "We Won't Pay! We Can't Pay!"
- Vancouver, spiral notebook, 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains handwritten notes, newspaper clippings, and segments of scripts for "We Can't Pay, We Won't Pay."
- Act I. - We Won't Pay, We Won't Pay - used Vancouver B.C., 1980 (Box 2)
  A spiral bound corrected script.
- Act II. - We Won't Pay, We Won't Pay, 1980 (Box 2)
- We Won't Pay - notebooks, circa 1981; 5 folders (Box 2)
- Vancouver - WWP, photographic negatives, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- We Won't Pay - Chelsea Theater, circa 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains bumper stickers, Showbills, and a flyer.
- New York - Los Angeles, notebook, 1980-1981 (Box 2)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (LAAT) letterhead, and newspaper clippings.
- N.Y. Reviews - WWP, circa 1980s (Box 2)
  Contains programs, newspaper clippings, handwritten and typescript notes, and photocopies.
- Master text - WWP / WWP, hand-corrected script, circa 1984 (Box 2)
- Casting - WWP, 1980-09 (Box 2)
  Contains two sprial notebooks, with handwritten and typescript notes, photographic prints, and correspondence.
- We Won't Pay - N.Y., circa 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, photographic prints, flyers and posters, correspondence, photocopies, and newspaper clippings.
- Vancouver - general, circa 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, photocopies and contact prints.
- Tamahnous / Vancouver contract (non si paga 1980), circa 1980 (Box 2)
  Contains correspondence, handwritten notes and typescript notes.
- WWP Vancouver, correspondence, 1980-09 (Box 2)
- Vancouver posters and flyers, 1982 (Box 2)
- Vancouver reviews, flyers, photocopies, and posters, 1980 (Box 2)
- Vancouver - correspondence, 1982 (Box 2)
- Original - Stage Managers - We Won't Pay, corrected script, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Set designs and related notes, photographic prints, and photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Theater Heute magazine, No. 10, 1978-10 (Box 2)
- We Won't Pay, photoprints for publication., circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Theater Heute magazine, No. 5, 1978-05 (Box 3)
- Lowlife, notebook of Randy Clark, 1990 (Box 3)
- Theater magazine, Yale School of Drama, circa 1983 (Box 3)
- Montreal, 1980 (Box 3)
  Contains letters between R. G. Davis and Maurice Pudbrey, as well as handwritten notes.
- 7 Anarch / California Confederation of the Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  Contains newsletter, correspondence, and a proof of "Seven Anarchists I Have Known: American Approaches to Dario Fo."
- Anarchist 7, 1985 (Box 3)
  Contains corrected typescript draft, correspondence, photocopies, and newspaper and magazine clippings.
- Contact print, undated (Box 3)
- Dario Fo - "Isabella...," corrected script, circa 1982 (Box 3)
- Dario Fo - "The Boss's Funeral," photocopied script, translated by Suzanne Cowan, circa 1979 (Box 3)
- Mothers, notebook and "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" flyer, 1982-02 (Box 3)
- Mothers - Open Circle, notebook, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- Mothers Marijuana - master, 1982 (Box 3)
  Script for "Mothers Marijuana is the Best." Also includes a newspaper clipping.
- Mothers Marijuana - contracts and correspondence, 1982 (Box 3)
- Sylvia's - Mother, corrected script, circa 1980s (Box 3)
- Mother Marijuana, corrected script, 1982-02 (Box 3)
- "Agnelli", circa 1980s (Box 3)
  Contains "Stand Up and (Bronx) Cheer!" script, translated from "Clacson, trombette e pernacchi," by Dale McAdoo and Charles Mann. Also contains a letter.
- Theatre Quarterly and New Theatre Quarterly, periodicals, 1981-1989 (Box 3)
  Contains Vol. X, No. 40 (1981) of Theatre Quarterly. Also contains Vol. I, No. 2 (1985 May), Vol. IV, No. 13 (1988 February) and Vol. V, No. 19 (1989 August) of New Theatre Quarterly.
- 5th Festival of Italian Theatre in New York, program, circa 1980 (Box 3)
  Contains a Welfare State International brouchure, the ripped cover of "Theater: Satire and Politics in the '70s" (1979 Spring), and We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay! flyers and programs.
- Spiral notebook, circa 1980 (Box 3)
- Il lavoro teatrale per «Vita di galileo», photostat copy, 1980-1984 (Box 3)
  Contains pages 295 through 326. Also contains Resolutions Committee, Leisure Time and the Arts, 26th Constitutional Convention, UAW, pamphlet (1980 June), an annoucement from The Labor Theater regarding "Left Out Lady" (1981 January 12), handwritten notes, a flyer from The Labor Theater regarding "Railroad Bill," a photoprint from the Seattle production of "We Won't Pay," newpaper and magazine clippings, and handouts regarding We Won't Pay! at the Old Spaghetti Factory (1983).
- Viareggio in Maschera: Carnevale nel Mondo, booklet, 1964 (Box 3)
- Mother's Marijuana, script, circa 1983 (Box 3)
  Also contains newspaper clippings, and another script of "Mother's Marijuana is the Best," translated by Tony Mitchell.
- Alexander H. Cohen, correspondence and newspaper clippings, circa 1982 (Box 3)
- Nora Marchi - Tony Mitchell - Margaret Kunzle, correspondence, circa 1979-1981 (Box 3)
- Open Circle Theatre - "Death of an Anarchist" prologue, circa 1980s-2008 (Box 3)
  Also contains a print-out of a 2008 booklist submission for a course taught by R. G. Davis at Univeristy of California, Davis.
- Fo / Mistero Buffo, circa 1980s (Box 3)
  Contains a photocopy of a printed overview of Mistero Buffo. Also contains a script for "The Resurrection of Lazarus," an English version of Mistero Buffo, translated by Charles Mann and Dale McAdoo.
- McAdoo and Mann, correspondence, circa 1983 (Box 3)
  Contains material regarding Dale McAdoo and Charles Mann. Also contains newspaper clippings, photocopies, and a corrected script for "It's All Church, Home and Bed."
- Dario Fo - scripts for Fruit of the Loom and The Boss's Funeral; Grand Pantomime, circa 1979-1980s (Box 3)
- The Militant Theatre of Dario Fo, by Suzanne Cowan, thesis, 1977-05 (Box 3)
- Ray Gaspard, correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
- "Other Dario Fo plays", circa 1980s (Box 3)
  Contains a Yale Repertory Theatre program, The Labor Theater newsletter regarding Left Out Lady, newspaper clippings, "Dario Fo: Bibliography, Biography, Playography," compiled by Suzanne Cowan, and correspondence.
- Dario Fo - Accidental Death of an Anarchist, circa 1980 (Box 3)
  Contains a photostat of an English script, translated by Tony Mitchell.
- Non si paga - Toronto, correspondence, photocopies, and handwritten notes, 1980 (Box 4)
- Persephone / Sask, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence and photocopies, regarding Persephone Theater, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada.
- Mixed Blood - dead, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence and photocopies, regarding Mixed Blood theatre company, Minneapolis, Minnesota.
- The Awakening (Il risveglio), corrected script, circa 1980s (Box 4)
  Contains a notes and an English script, translated by Charles Mann and Dale McAdoo.
- Empty Space - Seattle, 1981 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, flyers, photographic prints, and newspaper clippings, regarding the Empty Space theatre.
- Seattle, 1981-05 (Box 4)
  Contains handwritten notes, photostat copies, newspaper and magazine clippings, flyers, and maps.
- Southeastern Louisiana University, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, photographic prints, a newspaper, a poster, flyers and a program.
- Syracuse Stage, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, a program and flyers, financial information, photocopies and newspaper clippings.
- Hippodrome - Florida, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains handwritten notes, correspondence, financial information, programs and photocopies.
- Chocolate Bayou - Houston, Texas, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, photographic prints, photocopies, and programs.
- Reviews - Female Parts, 1982-1988 (Box 4)
  Contains newspaper clippings, programs, photocopies, and a copy of the San Francisco Focus magazine (1982 December).
- S.F. notes - dramatory ct. / Female Parts, 1982 (Box 4)
- Female Parts - stage material, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  Contains a photocopy of a corrected script, with production notes.
- Book II - Female Parts, notebook with photocopies and handwritten notes, 1982 (Box 4)
- Female-Parts - English text, notebook with handwritten and typescript notes, 1982 (Box 4)
- Other Productions - San Francisco, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains newspaper clippings, photocopies, press material, and correspondence.
- Other Theatre Cafe - contract letter and handwritten notes, 1982 (Box 4)
- Female Parts - contracts, Open Theatre Cafe, circa 1982 (Box 4)
- Iowa University - We Won't Pay, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, photocopies, photographic prints, and a University Theatres booklet regarding the 1982-1983 season.
- Regina / Globe and Magnus - WWP, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  Contains material associated with the Globe Theatre (Regina, Saskatchewan) and the Magnus Theatre (Thunder Bay, Ontario). Includes programs, photocopies, posters, flyers, a photographic print, correspondence and some finanical material.
- Penguin Theatre - Ottawa, Ontario, correspondence, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence regarding the Penguin Theatre (Ottawa, Ontario).
- James Madison University, correspondence, 1983 (Box 4)
- Wisdom Bridge Theatre - WWP, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains material related to the Wisdom Bridge Theatre (Chicago, Illinois). Includes newspaper clippings, correspondnece, handwritten notes, and programs.
- Female Parts - original stage manager book, 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains a corrected script, photocopies, and stage outlines.
- Jane Dornacker, circa 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, photocopies, and photographic prints.
- Female Parts - final accounts and financial material, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Detroit - James Moran, correspondence and newspaper clippings, circa 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- San Diego Public Theatre, correspondence, photocopies and pamphlet, 1982 (Box 4)
- Australia - We Won't Pay, 1980-1981 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, a poster and photographic prints.
- WWP WWP - Atlanta, program, photocopies, and mailer, 1986 (Box 4)
- WWP - inquires, newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Boston - Downing Cless, correspondence, flyers, photocopies, and photographic prints, 1982 (Box 4)
- White Rock, British Columbia, circa 1983 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence and photocopies, regarding the White Rock Summer Theatre (White Rock, British Columbia).
- Ann Arbor - performance - WWP, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains newspaper clippings, handwritten notes, programs, and flyers.
- Sumus - Portland, 1982 (Box 4)
  Contains correspondence, handwritten notes, and newspaper clippings, regarding the Sumus Theatre Ensemble (Portland, Oregon).
- Female Parts - stage manager notes, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  Contains material regarding a production of Female Parts, performed at the Open Theatre Cafe, with Jane Dornacker.
- WWP: bios, 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains biographies, as well as a notebook, photocopies, and a copy of the 1982 October 4 lease of the Victoria Theatre (San Francisco, California).
- Press - San Francisco reviews, press, and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 5)
- Payables - Female Parts, newspaper clippings and handwritten notes., 1982-1983 (Box 5)
- Female Parts - with Dario Fo, 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  Contains correspondence, handwritten and typescript notes, and financial material.
- Los Angeles Theatre magazine, 1981-1983 (Box 5)
  Contains an October 1981 issue of Los Angeles Theatre magazine. Also contains a letter from [Julie] to R. G. Davis and [Tom], dated 1983 February 4.
- LAAT - notes, 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains multiple copies of the Los Angeles Actor's Theatre newspaper (1981 September / October), as well as multiple copies of the Los Angeles Theatre magazine (1981 September). Also contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, and typescript notes.
- L.A. Reviews - We Won't Pay, photocopies and flyers, 1981 (Box 5)
- L.A. contracts - WWP, 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains correspondence, Los Angeles Theatre magazine (1981 September), Los Angeles Actors' Theatre newspaper (1981 June / July), a photographic print, Los Angeles Actors' Theatre material, and a showbill for "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!"
- LAAT - programs, 1982 (Box 5)
  Contains "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" material. Specifically, newspaper clippings, a showbill, a Los Angeles Theatre magazine (1981 October), and flyers.
- Joe Spano - L.A. Intro, newspaper clippings, photocopies, a flyer, and correspondence, 1987-09 (Box 5)
- Los Angeles - press, WWP, 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains photocopies, correspondence, newspaper clippings, a copy of the Los Angeles Theatre magazine (1981 September), and a copy of the Los Angeles Actors' Theatre newspaper (1981 September / October).
- Teatro Quatro-4, 1982 (Box 5)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, a notebook, photocopies, newsletters and correspondence.
- WWP - press / PR and program, 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains newspaper clippings, handwritten and typescript notes, photocopies, correspondence, financial materials, contact prints and photographic prints.
- Master - Intro - WWP, circa 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains newspaper clippings, "We Won't Pay!" showbill, photocopies, and handwritten and typescript notes.
- "Angelli," empty envelope, circa 1983 (Box 5)
- Production - S.F. - WWP, 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, correspondence, newspaper clippings, and a self-developing photograph.
- LAAT - WWP, notebook, 1981 (Box 5)
- "II" - WWP script, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
  Contains Act II of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," performed at the Chelsea Theatre, New York.
- "I" - WWP script, 1982 (Box 5)
  Contains Act I. of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," performed at Teatro 4, New York.
- "II" - WWP script, 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains Act II of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," performed at the Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (LAAT).
- "I" - WWP script, 1981 (Box 5)
  Contains Act I of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," performed at the Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (LAAT).
- Teatro 4 - WWP, Cuba, circa 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains empty Stage Directors and Choreographers Society (SDC) envelope.
- Book I - Female Parts S.F., notebook with drawings and financial material, 1982 (Box 5)
- Reviews - Rome, London, NY, L.A. - orig., circa 1982 (Box 5)
  Contains correspondence, newspaper clippings, and photocopies.
- Picture - Female Parts - Jane Dornacker, circa 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains photographs, contact prints and newspaper clippings.
- Production - Female Parts, handwritten and typescript notes, 1983 (Box 5)
- Español / WWP, 1982 (Box 5)
  Contains Spanish scripts of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!"
- San Francisco Chronicle, newspaper, 2017-07-06 (Box 5)
- Female Parts - final script, circa 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains various scripts, including The Awakening (Il Risveglio), Punk Momma (La mamma fricchettona), and We All Have the Same Story! (Abbiamo tutte la stessa storia).
- We Won't Pay - San Francisco version - Geoffrey Reeves, corrected scripts, 1983 (Box 5)
- WWP - San Franciso - dramaturgy, 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains Local 6 (ILWU) newsletter, handwritten and tyepscript notes, and newspaper clippings.
- WWP - Ellen Brooks - San Francisco, 1983-04 (Box 5)
  Contains magazine clipping, typescript notes and a script for "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!"
- WWP - San Francisco - stopped, 1983 (Box 5)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence, a copy of Theatre Communications (1982 September), and various curricula vitarum, with accompanying photographic headshots.
- Non si paga - Italiana, script, circa 1978 (Box 6)
- Dramaturgy - Non si paga and translation, circa 1983 (Box 6)
  Contains newspaper clippings, handwritten and typescript notes, a copy of the 5th Festival of Italian Theatre in New York catalog (1980), correspondence, and photocopies.
- Fo - accounts, financial materials and correspondence, 1981 (Box 6)
- Fo - accounts, correspondence, handwritten and typescript notes, and financial materials, 1982 (Box 6)
- Fo - accounts, financial material and correspondence, 1983 (Box 6)
- Italy, 1982 (Box 6)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, typed editorial notes regarding "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
- Dario Who? - Theatre Quarterly - BTB essay, 1981 (Box 6)
  Contains handwritten and typescript notes, correspondence, and corrected writings.
- We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!, Act. I, script, 1979-08 (Box 7)
  Contains the Suzanne Cowan and James Cowan English-language translation.
- We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!, Act II, script, 1979-08 (Box 7)
- Theatre Quarterly, Vol. IX, No. 35, photocopy, circa 1979 (Box 7)
- Dario Fo - visa, notebook, 1980-05 (Box 7)
- The Militant Theatre of Dario Fo, by Suzanne Cowan, 1977 (Box 7)
  Contains a bound typescript of chapter 6 through chapter 8.
- Notebooks, regarding "Non si paga, non si paga!", 1979 (Box 7)
- Music - Italian, circa 1976 (Box 7)
  Contains "Il Mio Album Italiano: Songs Children Sing in Italy", arranged by Victor Molil (1976).
- We Won't Pay - Act I., 1979 (Box 7)
  Contains a corrected typescript of Act I from "We Won't Pay, We Won't Pay," adapted by R. G. Davis.
- We Won't Pay - Act II., 1979 (Box 7)
  Contains a corrected typescript of Act II from "We Won't Pay, We Won't Pay," adapated by R. G. Davis.
- We Won't Pay - program notes - NYU, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  Contains newspaper clippings, flyers and programs, and a notebook.
- Whole Theatre Co, 1979 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding the Whole Theatre Company (Montclair, New Jersey), specifically correspondence, handwritten notes, and newspaper clippings.
- Shelley Winters - letters, 1979 (Box 7)
- Notes and letters - Marino Regini and Erika Munk, corrected typescripts, 1972 (Box 7)
- We Won't Pay - letters, 1979 (Box 7)
- We Won't Pay - notes and letters, 1982 (Box 7)
- LAAT - We Won't Pay, 1981 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding the Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (LAAT), specifically contact prints, photographic prints and flyers.
- Sam French - copy for text publication, 1986 (Box 7)
  Contains the script for "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," as well as correspondence and photocopies.
- English text - Female Parts, scripts and photocopies, circa 1982 (Box 7)
- Bezahlt wird nicht! - Non si paga, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  Contains photographs, handwritten and typescript notes, correspondence, and photocopies.
- Dario Fo - letters and contracts, 1979 (Box 7)
  Includes a "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" showbill.
- We Won't Pay - NYU - Town Hall, 1980 (Box 7)
  Contains photocopies, programs, handwritten and typescript notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence, and a copy of "5th Festival of Italian Theatre in New York" (1980).
- Meinhoff / News, undated (Box 7)
  Contains English scripts for "Ulrike Meinhoff... Sex... Female... Communist," as well as "Tomorrow's News," translated by Tony Mitchell.
- Anarchist - NYU, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  Contains a typed program for "Accidental Death of an Anarchist."
- Berliner ensemble - Non si paga / Bezahlt wird nicht!, handwritten notes, 1979 (Box 7)
- Anarchist - L.A. / Washington D.C./ San Francisco / New York, 1983-1984 (Box 7)
  Contains magazine and newspaper clippings, photocopies and correspondence.
- We Can't Pay - English - Criterion Theatre, 1982 (Box 7)
  Contains material related to the Criterion Theatre (London, United Kingdom), including correspondence, photocopies, newspaper clippings and scripts.
- Barry Freed - Abbie Hoffman, letter, 1982 (Box 7)
- Cowan, Suzanne / Kidron, Michael - translation, publication, 1979 (Box 7)